Guide to the Marilyn Symmes Collection of Art Exhibition Ephemera 1973-2019 (bulk 1990s-2019) PR 352
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Single Artist Exhibitions, 1973-2019 (bulk 1990s-2019)
  - Hon-Hy, 1994-2015 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Roni Horn, Sabine Hornig, Thomas Houseago, Zhang Huan, and Pierre Huyghe.
  - H (Set 2), 1999-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 10)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, Peter Halley, Ann Hamilton, Jane Hammond, Stephen Hannock, Duane Hanson, Alex Harsley, Marsden Hartley, Daniel Heidkamp, Michael Heizer, Barbara Hepworth, Anthony Hernandez, David Hockney, Loie Hollowell, John Hoyland, Peter Hujar, Su-Li Hung, and Frances Hynes. Also includes a pamphlet from the Museum of Fine Arts, Houston -- a 2002 Core Yearbook on Trenton Doyle Hancock which includes a biography on the artist. Also includes an advertisement of a film on the Artist, Eva Hesse, which includes a short biography of the artist. Includes a pamphlet from the Cade Tompkins Projects, Providence, Rhode Island, on the artist, Orit Hofshi. Icludes a Hammer Project pamphlet on Alex Hubbard, complete with a biography of the artist. Includes a Studio Museum in Harlem exhibition poster on "Richard Hunt: Framed and Extended."
  - I, 2003-2016 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Jorg Immendorff and Robert Irwin.
  - I (Set 2), 2018-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 11)
    Includes materials from artists, including, Christina Iglesias, Mark Innerst, Robert Irwin, and Kenro Izu.
  - Ja-Je, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Matthew Day Jackson and Neil Jenney. Also includes the Pace Wildenstein 1995 exhibition catalogue for Alfred Jensen Where the Gods Reside: Paintings 1963-1968.
  - Ji-Ju, 1994-2016 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Jasper Johns, Ynez Johnston, and Donald Judd. Also includes a Print Club 1994 exhibition catalogue for Lois M. Johnson Latitudes, 1984-1994, and a Francis M. Naumann 2005 exhibition catalogue for Don Joint Catawumpus.
  - J (Set 2), 2001-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 12)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, Dakota Jackson, Yvonne Jacquette, Alfred Jensen, Chris Johanson, Rashid Johnson, and William H. Johnson. Also includes a National Gallery of Art, Washington, Bullentin on the exhibition, "Jasper Johns: Prints from Four Decades." Also includes a poster from the Donald Judd Foundation, explaining the foundation and also presenting a biography of Donald Judd.
  - Ka, 1994-2016 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Ilya and Emilia Kabakov, Frida Kahlo, Anish Kapoor, Alex Katz. Also includes a Walker Art Center 2008 exhibition catalogue Frida Kahlo, a Museum of Modern Art 1995 exhibition brochure Kandinsky Compositions, and a Guggenheim 2015 exhibition checklist, On Kawara -- Silence.
  - Ke, 1994-2015 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Mike Kelley, Ellsworth Kelly, William Kentridge. Also includes a Hirshhorn Museum 2001 exhibition catalogue William Kentridge, a Getty Museum 1994 exhibition catalogue Andre Kertesz: A Centennial Tribute, and a Dieu Donne 2008 interview with Jon Kessler.
  - Kh-Kn, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Anselm Kiefer, William Klein, Gustav Klimt, and Franz Kline.
  - Ko, 1999-2016 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Jeff Koons and Harmony Korine. Also includes a Galerie St. Etienne 2013 exhibition catalogue for Kathe Kollwitz The Complete Print Cycles, and a Grey Art Gallery (NYU) 2003 exhibition catalogue for Paul Kos Everything Matters/ A Retrospective.
  - Kr-Kw, 2001-2016 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Lee Krasner, Walt Kuhn, Guillermo Kuitca, and Yayoi Kusama. Also includes a Barbara Mathes Gallery 2007 exhibition catalogue for Yayoi Kusama From Here to Infinity, and a Whitney Museum 2012 exhibition catalogue, Yayoi Kusama.
  - K (Set 2), 1996-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 13)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, Ilya & Emilia Kababov, Wolf Kahn, Amar Kanwar, Alex Katz, Betsy Kaufman, Mike Kelley, Michael Kenna, Byron Kim, Martin Kippenberger, Ragnar Kjartansson, Mark Klett, Dorothy Koppelman, Victor Kord, Joyce Kozloff, Max Kozloff, Yayoi Kusama, Robert Kushner, and Su Kwak. Also includes a fold-out board for the exhibition, "Jitish Kallat: Decimal Point." Includes a Met sheet on "Sara Berman's Closet" by the artist, Maira Kalman. Also includes a brochure from Highpoint Center for Printing on the artist, Michael Kareken, with a biography. Also includes a MOMA Kids Family Activity Guide to the exhibition, "William Kentridge: Five Themes." Includes a bookmark designed by Alison Knowles. Includes a pamphlet for a program put on by Stonybrook University on the Art and Life of Lee Krasner.
  - La-Lep, 1991-2016 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Gaston Lachaise, Wolfgang Laib and Jacob Lawrence. Also includes a Sperone Westwater 2015 exhibition catalogue Helmut Lang, a Hirschl & Adler Modern 2005 exhibition catalogue for Nancy Lawton Drawings in Sterling Silver, an Archives of American Art 1991 exhibition catalogue for Blanche Lazzell: A Modernist Rediscovered, and a Dahn Gallery 1995 exhibition catalogue for Annette Lemieux: Works from 1987-1992.
  - LeWitt, Sol, 2004-2016 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
    Includes, among other documents, the prospectus for Squarings, a book of poems by Seamus Heaney with drawings by LeWitt, a MassMoCA 2008 Gallery Guide for Sol LeWitt: A Wall Drawing Retrospective, and a PaceWildenstein 2009 booklet Sol LeWitt: Forms Derived from a Cube, Wall Drawing #420B.
  - Ler-Liz, 1994-2015 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Sandra Lerner, Helen Levitt, Roy Lichtenstein, and Maya Lin. Also includes an invitation to a 2003 Edgar Levy show at Susan Teller Gallery with a price list for his works.
  - Lo-Ly, 1999-2015 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Whitfield Lovell, Markus Lupertz, and Vera Lutter.
  - L (Set 2), 1989-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 14)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, Wolfgang Laib, Helmut Lang, Jacob Lawrence, An-My Le, Richard Learoyd, Charles Ledray, Sandra Lerner, Sherrie Levine, Alain Licari, Roy Lichtenstein, Maya Lin, James Little, Richard Long, Andrew Lord, Tim Lovejoy, Whitfield Lovell, and David Lynch. Also includes a fold-out board on the exhibition, "Michael Landy: Breaking News - New York." Includes a poster from the exhibition, "Norman Lewis: Looking East." Also includes a pamphlet from the International Center of Photography, "Alexander Liberman: The Artist in his Studio." Includes a pamphlet on the Artist, Emil Lukas, in connection with an exhibition of his works held at the Sperone Westwater Gallery.
  - Mab-Map, 1996-2016 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Heinz Mack, Loren Maclver, Robert Mangold, Sally Mann, and Robert Mapplethorpe. Also includes a Harwood Museum of Art 2012 exhibition catalogue for Bea Mandelman:The Social Realist Prints, and a David Findlay Jr Gallery 2013 exhibition catalogue for Beatrice Mandelman:Works from the 1950s-1960s.
  - Mar-Maz, 2005-2016 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Brice Marden, Herman Maril, John Marin, and Agnes Martin. Also includes a Mary Ryan Gallery 2010 exhibition checklist for Michael Mazur Pond Edge and David Findlay Jr. Gallery 2015 exhibition catalogue for Emily Mason.
  - Me-Mi, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Julie Mehretu, Mario Merz, Annette Messager, Joel Meyerowitz, Duane Michals, and Richard Misrach.
  - Mo, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Paula Moderson-Becker, Frank Moore, Henry Moore, Malcolm Morley, and Marie-Louise Motesiczky.
  - Mu, 2006-2016 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Edvard Munch, Vik Muniz, Oscar Munoz, Takashi Murakami, Catherine Murphy, and Elizabeth Murray.
  - Mc, 2006-2015 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Paul McCarthy, Ryan McGinness, John McLaughlin, Laura McPhee, and Steve McQueen. Also includes a David Findlay Jr. Gallery 2013 exhibition catalogue for Robert McChesney.
  - M (Set 2) (2 folders), 1987-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 15-16)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, George Maciunas, Heinz Mack, Loren MacIver, Robert Mangold, Sally Mann, John Marin, Alpha and Chris Mason (Hipkiss), Gordon Matta-Clark, James McCracken Jr., Ralph Eugene Meatyard, Julie Mehretu, Jonas Mekas, Prabhavathi Meppayil, Hugh Mesibov, Duane Michals, Santi Moix, Marc de Montebello, Katy Moran, Malcolm Morley, Robert Morris, Carrie Moyer, Matt Mulligan, and Juan Munoz. Also includes a fold-out sheet on a Lisa Mackie exhibition, "Here Then and Now" with a biography of the artist. Also includes a Whitney Museum of American Art poster on the public program, "Christian Marclay: Festival." Includes a Tate Modern guide to the 2015 Agnes Martin exhibition. Includes a DIA:Chelsea information guide on the exhibition, "Rita McBride: Particulates." Includes a David Nolan Gallery guide to an exhibition of Works by Wardell Milan with a biography of the artist. Includes a Jewish Museum, New York pamphlet on the exhibition, "Using Floors, Walls, and Ceilings: Beatriz Milhazes", with a short biography of the artist. Includes sveral Jewish Museum, New York gallery guides and Kids gallery guides to the exhibition, "Isaac Mizrahi: An Unruly History." Includes an excerpt of an interview with the artist Karabo Poppy Molestane as the artist prepared to paint the Art Wall at the UC Berkley Art Museum and Pacific Film Archive. Also includes a NYU Grey Art Gallery brochure on public programs around two exhibitions of work by Charlotte Moorman. Includes a DIA:Chelsea information guide on the exhibition of works by Francois Morellet. Includes a NYU Grey Art Gallery brochure on public programs around the exhibition, "Mark Mothersbaugh: Myopia."
  - Na-Ne, 1991-2015 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
    Includes materials for artists, including, among others, Elie Nadelman, Nabil Nahas, Bruce Nauman, Alice Neel, Louise Nevelson, Henry Roderick Newman, nd Barnett Newman. Also includes a David Findlay Jr. Gallery 2006 exhibition catalogue for Robert Natkin.
  - Ni-Noz, 1994-2016 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Nicholas Nixon, Paul Noble, Isamu Noguchi, and Thomas Nozkowski. Also includes a Salander-O'Reilly Galleries exhibition catalogue for Graham Nickson, a 2003 Isamu Noguchi Foundation exhibition catalogue Noguchi Contours, and a few other Noguchi Museum publications.
  - N (Set 2), 1996-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 17)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, Laurel Nakadate, Bruce Nauman, Jim Nawara, Eduardo Navarro, Alice Neel, Emily Nelligan, Kenneth Noland, Todd Norsten, Reynier Leyva Novo, and Thomas Nozkowski. Also includes a poster for the exhibition, "Yoshitomo Mara: Thinker." Also includes an information brochure on The Isamu Noguchi Garden Museum. Includes a Museum at FIT pamphlet on the exhibition, "Norell: Dean of American Fashion."
  - O, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
    Includes materials for artists, including, among others, Albert Oehlen, Helio Oiticica, Claes Oldenburg, Yoko Ono, Gabriel Orozco, and Tom Otterness.
  - O (Set 2), 2000-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 18)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, The Oakes Twins, Jill O'Bryan, Chris Ofili, Claes Oldenburg, Yoko Ono, and Alfonso Ossorio.
  - Pa-Par, 2000-2015 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
    Includes materials for artists, including, among others, Nam June Paik, Sky Pape, Aaron Parazette, and Betty Parsons. Also includes a 2000 Guggenheim Guide to Guggenheim Museums, a Chesterwood 2014 exhibition catalogue for Albert Paley, a Lisa Sette Gallery 2014 exhibition catalogue for Luis Gonzalez Palma, a Whitney 2010 exhibition catalogue for Karthik Pandian, a FIT Art and Design Faculty 2011 exhibition catalogue for a Kingsley Parker installation Upriver, a W.M. Brady 2005 exhibition catalogue for Simon Parkes, and a Park Avenue Armory 2015 exhibition catalogue for Philippe Parreno.
  - Pas-Pey, 2002-2016 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Jaanika Peerna, A.R. Penck, Gelah Penn, Irving Penn, Emilio Perez, Raymond Pettibon, and Elizabeth Peyton. Also includes a 2014 Gagosian Gallery exhibition catalogue for Giuseppe Penone, a Marian Goodman Gallery 2015 exhibition catalogue for Giuseppe Penone, and a Gagosian Gallery 2016 exhibition catalogue for Giuseppe Penone.
  - Pf-Pow, 2002-2016 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Ellen Phelan, Richard Phillips, Sarah Plimpton, and Charlotte Posenenske. Also includes a Whitney 2016 exhibition catalogue for Laura Poitras, a MoMA 2014 exhibition catalogue for Sigmar Polke, a Washburn Gallery 2003 exhibition catalogue for Jackson Pollock, and a Childs Gallery 2010 exhibition catalogue for Anne Lyman Powers.
  - Picasso, 2003-2016 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
    Includes material related to Pablo Picasso exhibitions.
  - Pr-Q, 2003-2015 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Debra Priestly, Richard Prince, and Martin Puryear. Also includes a MoMA 2007 exhibition catalogue for Martin Puryear.
  - P (Set 2) (2 folders), 2003-2019 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 19-20)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, Adrian Paci, Wendy Paton, Ebony G. Patterson, Irving Penn, Raymond Pettibon, Sarah Plimpton, Richard Pousette-Dart, and Richard Prince. Also includes a foldout on a Sky Pape exhibition, "Water Works: Surface Tensions New Drawings." Includes a 2016 The Met sheet on "The Rooftop Garden Commission: Cornelia Parker Transitional Object (PsychoBarn)." Also includes a few Giuseppe Penone catalogues of the Marian Goodman Gallery and the Gagosian Gallery. Includes a Cade Tompkins Projects card for the exhibition, "Aaron Pexa: The Lucent Parlor" with a biography of the artist. Includes a brochure published by the Taipei American School Art Gallery to accompany the exhibition, "The Adventure of Endi Poskovic." Includes a MOMA catalogue from the 2007 exhibition of works by Martin Puryear.
  - Ra, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Paul Rand, Karim Rashid, Robert Rauschenberg, and Man Ray.
  - Re-Rich, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Ad Reinhardt, Sam Reveles, Terry Richardson, and Gerhard Richter. Also includes an excerpt written by Prudence Peiffer on Ad Reinhardt's Projected Non-Happenings, and a Bernard Goldberg Fine Arts Gallery 2006 exhibition catalogue for Winold Reiss.
  - Rin-Ros, 1981-2016 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Dorothea Rockburne, James Rosenquist, Clifford Ross, Medardo Rosso, and Theodore Roszak.
  - Rot-Ry, 1993-2015 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Dieter Roth, Susan Rothenberg, Barbara Roux, Michal Rovner, Sterling Ruby, Thomas Ruff, Christ Rupp, and Robert Ryman.
  - Ruppersberg, Allen, 2013 (Offsite-box 22, Item 1)
    Includes a boxed scroll (and explanatory note) from Gemini G.E.L. that documents Ruppersberg's work Great Speckled Bird on exhibition at the gallery. The scroll is signed and dated by Ruppersberg. Access restriction: The object can be unrolled only with the assistance of the conservator; advance arrangements are required.
  - Ruscha, Ed, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artist, Ed Ruscha, including a Whitney Museum catalogue for Ed Ruscha's 2005 Venice Biennale installation for the U.S. Pavilion.
  - R (Set 2), 1983-2018 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 21)
    Includes materials from artists, including, among others, Edi Rama, Robert Rauschenberg, Josh Reames, Lilly Reich, Alexis Rockman, Claire Rosen, Mark Rothko, Michael Rovner, Nancy Rubins, Ed Ruscha, and Robert Ryman. Also includes a Weisman Art Museum/Minneapolis Institute of the Arts brochure on the retrospective exhibition, "Ralph Rapson: Sixty Years of Modern Design." Includes a brochure on "Speak, An Exhibition of Work by Ellen Rothenberg." Also includes a Los Angeles County Museum of Art brochure on Susan Rothenberg, including a biography of the artists and several exhibitions.
  - Sa-Sal, 1996-2016 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Betye Saar and Tom Sachs. Also includes a Finnish Cultural Institute in New York 2002 exhibition catalogue for Eero Saarinen: Realizing American Utopia.
  - Sam-Scha, 1997-2016 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Lucas Samaras, Fred Sandback, and Jenny Saville. Also includes a Kristen Frederickson Contemporary Art 2004 exhibition catalogue Miriam Schapiro: A Retrospective.
  - Sche-Sha, 1994-2015 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Julian Schnabel, Thomas Schutte, Joel Shapiro, and Willoughby Sharp. Also includes a Guggenheim Museum Willoughby Sharp Memorial program from 2009; text of a poem Paradise: A Dear Sip (That's Sweetheart, not Bambi) for Willoughby Sharp & Pamela Seymour Smith Sharp, written by Verandah Porche, with Porche's notes regarding the poem (dated 12 October 2009); and a Susan Teller Gallery 2003 exhibition checklist for Bernarda Bryson Shahn: Seventy-five Years of Work on Paper: 1928-2003.
  - Seltzer, Phyllis - Correspondence, 1993-2015 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
    Includes correspondence, including exhibition invitations and brochures, between Phyllis Seltzer and Marilyn Symmes regarding Seltzer's work and heat transfer process. Also includes a Butler Institute of American Art 2011 catalogue for Phyllis Seltzer: Scapes. Also includes a sheet of slides with images of works by Phyllis Seltzer and her assistant Zoya Trofimova (1993-2001).
  - Seltzer, Phyllis - Prints, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
    Includes 14 original prints by Phyllis Seltzer, some undated.
  - Serra, Richard, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artist Richard Serra.
  - She-Sim, 2004-2016 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Fazal Sheikh (2016 exhibition newspaper in English, Arabic and Hebrew for Erasures, and a brochure for Desert Bloom, the "central work" of Erasures), Cindy Sherman, Yinka Shonibare, James Siena, Laurie Simmons, and Taryn Simon.
  - Sin-Sny, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, David Smith and Joan Snyder. Also includes a Susan Teller Gallery 2004 exhibition listing for Mitchell Siporin and a Robert Miller Gallery 2009 program for Patti Smith: Veil, An Evening of Words and Song.
  - Soa-Ste, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Alec Soth, Michael Spano, and Frank Stella. Also includes a Smith College Museum of Art 2014 exhibition guide for Anne Whiston Spirn: The Eye is a Door.
  - Sti-Sz, 1989-2016 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Alfred Stieglitz, Rudolf Stingel, Thomas Struth, and Hiroshi Sugimoto. Also includes a Getty Museum 2005 exhibition catalogue brochure for Paul Strand: Three Roads Taken.
  - S (Set 2) (2 folders), 1981-2019 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1-2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Analia Saban, Tom Sachs, Anri Sala, Samaras, Katia Santibanez, Julian Schnabel, Thomas Schutte, Jonathan Seliger, Andrew Sendor, Richard Serra, Andres Serrano, Ben Shahn, Joel Shapiro, Willoughby Sharp, Raqib Shaw, Claire Sherman, Paul Shore, James Siena, Lorna Simpson, Raghubir Singh, Lucy Skaer, David Smith, Kiki Smith, Tony Smith, Joan Snyder, Frederick Sommer, Li Songsong, Keith Sonnier, Michael Stamm, Doug and Mike Starn, Pat Steir, Frank Stella, Rudolf Stingel, Myron Stout, Thomas Struth, Michelle Stuart, and Swoon. Also includes The Brooklyn Museum brochure on the Grand Lobby Installation, "The Woods Within" by Alison Saar. Also includes a National Academy of Design brochure on its 1992 exhibition, "Helene Schjerfbeck: Finland's Modernist Rediscovered". Includes a Storm King Art Center sheet on its 2019 exhibition, "Outlooks: Jean Shin". Includes a Guild Hall brochure on "Taryn Simon: The Innocents" and a Gagrosian Gallery brochure on "Contraband: Taryn Simon". Also includes a Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago Permanent Collection brochure on "Charles Simonds: Dwellings". Includes a Gitterman Gallery Henry Holmes Smith exhibition notice with a short biography of the artist. Includes a Jewish Museum Gallery Guide of the 2018 exhibition, "Chaim Soutine: Flesh". Includes a Jewish Museum brochure on the 2013 exhibition, "Art Spiegelman's Co-Mix A Retrospective". Also includes a Japan Society brochure on the exhibition, "Hiroshi Sugimoto: Gates of Paradise" with an Artist's Statement. Includes a Highpoint Center for Printmaking brochure on the exhibition, "Carolyn Swiszcz: New Suburban Mysteries" with a price list.
  - Ta-Te, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Philip Taaffe, Barbara Takenaga, Mark Tansey, and Antoni Tapies. Also includes a NYU Grey Art Gallery 2004 exhibition catalogue for Atsuko Tanaka: Electrifying Art and a Kent Gallery 2005 exhibition checklist for Dorothea Tanning: Insomnias.
  - Th-To, 1998-2016 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Robert Therrien, Frank Thiel, Fred Tomaselli, Niele Toroni, and Helen Torr. Also includes a Tiffany 1999 catalogue Highlights from the Tiffany & Co. Archives, and D.C. Moore Gallery 1998 and 1999 exhibition catalogues for George Tooker.
  - Tr-Ty, 2000-2016 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Diane Tuft, James Turrell, Richard Tuttle, Luc Tuymans, and Keith Tyson. Also includes a Doris C. Freedman Plaza (Central Park) 2015 exhibition catalogue for Tatiana Trouve: Desired Lines, a I-20 Gallery 2000 exhibition catalogue for Spencer Tunick: Reaction Zone, and a 2005 Whitney exhibition guide for The Art of Richard Tuttle.
  - Turrell, James, 2004 (Offsite-box 22, Item 2)
    Boxed light stick (unused) for exhibition at PaceWildenstein
  - Twombly, Cy, 1995-2015 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artist Cy Twombly, including a MoMA 1995 exhibition guide for Cy Twombly: A Retrospective.
  - T (Set 2), 1982-2019 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)